General
将軍
General Shilang
石狼将軍
Everything in the city has been arranged
城内の手配はすべて整え申した
There are agents in the city to assist
内通者ありて
The northern garrison
城北の守兵は
Most are already dead drunk
大半泥酔せり
Two warriors
二人の勇士は
Will open the city gates soon
間もなく城門を開き
To welcome the general into the city
将軍を迎え入れ申さん
Good dog
よい犬よ
You'll be rewarded
褒美を与えようぞ！
Thank you, General
将軍に感謝申し上げます。
Prepare the army
軍を整えよ
Ready for the assault
夜襲の準備をせよ
Yes
承知
General
将軍
Your subordinate
下は
For the general
将軍のため
Would naturally die a thousand deaths
命を捨てる覚悟にて候
But
然れど
Could you release my
我の妻と娘を
Wife and daughter first?
先に解放いただけぬか……
Of course
よかろう
I'll not only release them
お前の妻と娘を解放し
But also have a dozen Wuzhao warriors
十余名の鄔奴勇士が
Take good care of them
もてなすがよい
General, count me in
将軍、俺も一人分に加えてくれ！
Count me in too
俺も！
Good
よし！
Courageous
度胸ある者よ！
Shilang
石狼
You're a beast
お前は畜生だ！
You beast
畜生だ！
Xuan people
宣人は
A bunch of soft worms in the dirt
地を這う虫のごとし
Wuzhao warriors
鄔趙の勇士たち
Who dares to be the vanguard?
先陣志す者はおらぬか！
I will
俺がやる！
Good
よし！
I'll give you a unit
一隊を与えよう
Break the city today
今宵、城を破れ！
Yes
承知！
The gates are moving
門が動いた
Brothers
仲間ら
Follow me in the charge
俺について突撃せよ！
Gold, silver, and treasures
金銀財宝を
We'll take first
先に奪い取るぞ！
Why are there people
人影なし！
Something's not right
何かおかしいぞ！
We've been tricked
罠にかかったか!?
Fire arrows
矢を放て！
The enemy is trapped
賊、まるで壺の中に入り込んだかのごとし
Kill
討て！！
Report
報告！
General
将軍
The troops we just sent out
先ほど派遣した部隊
Have been completely wiped out
全滅せり！
What?
何だと？
Everyone, speak up
言え！
What should we do?
どうすればよいと申すか！
General
将軍
Perhaps Prince of Jin
恐らく晋王殿下が
Saw through our plan
我らの策を見抜かれ
And turned it against us
逆手に取られしものかと……
Do you think I'm blind?
我を愚か者と思うか？
Call them back
全員、撤退せよ
General, calm your anger
将軍、憤り給うなかれ！
This plan
この策
Isn't a complete failure yet
まだ終わりにあらずと存じます
As I know
拙者が承るところによれば
The Wuyang commander Chen Ying
午陽の守将・陳応の
Is backed by
裏には
Xuan Kingdom's Prince of Ning
宣国・寧王があって
Who doesn't get along with Prince of Jin
晋王殿下と不和と伝わっております
We can spread the false news that Prince of Jin
「晋王、失せた伝国璽を得たり」
Got the seal
との偽情報を流せば
To Wuyang
午陽を動揺させられましょう
You Xuan people
さすが宣人は
Understand Xuan people
宣人を知るな
Do as he says
言う通りにせよ
Also
また
Have those who came line up
来させたやつらを整列させよ
Yes
承知！